Guide to the Southern Tier Central Planning and Development Board reports, 1968-1990
Southern Tier Central Planning and Development Board reports, 1968-1990
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Southern Tier Central Planning and Development Board Reports, 1968-1990
4476
Southern Tier Central Planning and Development Board
3 cubic ft.
Planning reports and other documents.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Planning reports from the New York State Legislative Commission on Rural Resources, New York State Energy Research and Development Authority, New York State Office of Planning Coordination, New York State Temporary State Commission to Study the Catskills, Southern Tier Regional Planning and Development Board, Southern Tier West Regional Planning and Development Board, Capital District Regional Planning Commission, Central New York Regional Planning and Development Board, and Genesee/Finger Lakes Regional Planning Council, as well as planning reports from Chemung and Steuben Counties, and miscellaneous planning documents.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Planning reports from the New York State Legislative Commission on Rural Resources, New York State Energy Research and Development Authority, New York State Office of Planning Coordination, New York State Temporary State Commission to Study the Catskills, Southern Tier Regional Planning and Development Board, Southern Tier West Regional Planning and Development Board, Capital District Regional Planning Commission, Central New York Regional Planning and Development Board, and Genesee/Finger Lakes Regional Planning Council, as well as planning reports from Chemung and Steuben Counties, and miscellaneous planning documents.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Southern Tier Central Planning and Development Board (N.Y.); New York (State). Legislature. Legislative Commission on Rural Resources.; New York State Energy Research and Development Authority.; New York (State). Office of Planning Coordination.; New York (State). Temporary State Commission to Study the Catskills.; Southern Tier West Regional Planning and Development Board.; Capital District Regional Planning Commission.; Central New York Regional Planning and Development Board.; Genesee/Finger Lakes Regional Planning Council.
Subjects:
Regional planning--New York (State); Regional planning--New York (State)--Chemung County.; Regional planning--New York (State)--Steuben County.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. NYS, Legislative Commission on Rural Resources
Box 1
Series II. NYS, Energy Research and Development Authority (ERDA)
Box 1
Series III. NYS, Office of Planning Coordination
Box 1
Series IV. NYS, Temporary State Commission to Study the Catskills
Box 1
Series V. Southern Tier East Regional Planning and Development Board
Box 1
Series VI. Southern Tier Central Regional Planning and Development Board
Box 1
Series VII. Southern Tier West Regional Planning and Development Board
Box 2
Series VIII. Capital District Regional Planning Commission
Box 2
Series IX. Central New York Regional Planning and Development Board
Box 2
Series X. Genesee/Finger Lakes Regional Planning Council
Box 2
Series XI. Chemung County planning documents
Box 2
Series XII. Steuben County planning documents
Box 2
Series XIII. Miscellaneous planning documents
Box 3
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. NYS, Legislative Commission on Rural Resources
  - Eberts, Paul R. Socioeconomic Trends in Rural NYS: Towards the 21st Century, Sept. 1984 (Box 1)
  - Transportation in Rural NYS: An Action Strategy, May 2, 1985 (Box 1)
  - Community Facilities, Housing, and Community Renewal in Rural NYS: An Action Strategy, Apr. 10, 1985 (Box 1)
  - Agriculture in Rural NYS: An Action Strategy, May 2, 1985 (Box 1)
  - Health Care in Rural NYS: An Action Strategy, June 7, 1985 (Box 1)
  - Environment, Land Use and Natural Resources in Rural NYS: An Action Strategy, July 12, 1985 (Box 1)
  - Elementary, Secondary and Higher Education in Rural NYS: An Action Strategy, Sept. 11, 1985 (Box 1)
- Series II. NYS, Energy Research and Development Authority (ERDA)
  - 78-6, Assessment of Hydropower ... (Box 1)
  - 80-10, Hydropower Utilization in NYS (Box 1)
  - 80-22, Ethanol Production in Northern NY [CU] (Box 1)
  - 81-3, Ethanol Production in Southwester NY [CU] (Box 1)
  - 81-7, Ethanol Production in Southern Tier ... [CU] (Box 1)
  - 81-14, Geothermal Energy ... in Appalachin Basin of NYS (Box 1)
  - 82-1, Resource Engineering ... of Geothermal Energy (Box 1)
  - 82-10, Alternative ... Incentives ... of Ethanol ... in NYS [CU] (Box 1)
  - 82-28, An Analysis of ... Ethanol ... in Three NYS Regions [CU] (Box 1)
  - 83-4, ... Geothermal Reservoirs in Central and Western NYS (Box 1)
  - 83-24, Commercial ... Wood Gasification ... in NYS (Box 1)
  - 84-18, Auburn ... Geothermal Well (Box 1)
- Series III. NYS, Office of Planning Coordination
  - Central NY Regional Economic Study, Phase I, 1968 (Box 1)
  - Central NY Regional Economic Study, Phase II, 1969 (Box 1)
  - Black River/St. Lawrence Regional Economic Study, 1969 (Box 1)
  - NYS Appalachian Development Plan, 1971 (Box 1)
  - NYS Appalachian ... A Multi-year Investment Strategy, 1973 (Box 1)
- Series IV. NYS, Temporary State Commission to Study the Catskills
  - Final Report: The Future of the Catskills, 1975 (Box 1)
- Series V. Southern Tier East Regional Planning and Development Board
  - Annual Report, 1971-1976 (Box 1)
  - Regional Plan, Broome-Tioga Counties, Housing, 1971 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report for Tioga and Broome Counties, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Semi-Annual Program Activity Report, July-Sept. 1972, July-Sept. 1974 (Box 1)
  - Proposed Five Year Investment Plan, 1973-1974 (Box 1)
  - Growth Areas, Vol. 1, Population, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Growth Areas, Vol. 5, Summary, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Initial Regional Development Guide [Map], 1972 (Box 1)
- Series VI. Southern Tier Central Regional Planning and Development Board
  - Annual Report, 1970-1978 (Box 1)
  - Regional Profile, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Local Development District, Semi-Annual Report, Jan. 15, 1975 (Box 1)
  - Local Development District, Annual Report, July 15, 1975 (Box 1)
  - Proceedings of the Revenue Sharing Conference, Feb. 27, 1973 (Box 1)
  - Status Report/Housing Development Activities, Sept. 14, 1973 (Box 1)
  - Public Finance Study: Report No. 4, ... Capital Budgeting in the Corning-Elmira Area, 1975-1980, Nov. 1974 (Box 1)
  - Multi-Year Investment Report, May 1972, May 1973 (Box 1)
  - Renewable Energy Technology Handbook (2 copies), Dec. 1978 (Box 1)
  - Energy Technology Assessment Workbook (2 copies), Dec. 1978 (Box 1)
  - Energy Conservation and Development Plan (2 copies), July 1979 (Box 1)
- Series VII. Southern Tier West Regional Planning and Development Board
  - Annual Report, 1975-1981, 1984-1985, 1987 (Box 2)
  - Areawide Action Plan, 1979-1981 (Box 2)
  - Regional Land Use Plan, 1980 (Box 2)
  - Forest Industries Feasibility Study, Vol. I Timber Resources and ... Facilities (Box 2)
  - Forest Industries Feasibility Study, Vol. II, Financial Analysis ... (Box 2)
- Series VIII. Capital District Regional Planning Commission
  - Annual Report, 1969-1970, 1984, 1986, 1988 (Box 2)
  - The State of the Region, 1975 (Box 2)
  - Economic Study, 1970 (Box 2)
- Series IX. Central New York Regional Planning and Development Board
  - Annual Report, 1974, 1977, 1979-1981, 1986 (Box 2)
- Series X. Genesee/Finger Lakes Regional Planning Council
  - Annual Report, 1970-1972, 1979 (Box 2)
  - Comprehensive Regional Development Plan, A Summary, 1975 (Box 2)
  - Basic Study Series, Report #2, Economic Analysis (Box 2)
  - Basic Study Series, Report #9, Land Use (Box 2)
- Series XI. Chemung County planning documents
  - ... Planning Board, Annual Report, 1968, 1979, 1981 (Box 2)
  - Executive Transportation Committee ..., Policy Report, 1981-1982 (Box 2)
  - Executive Transportation Committee ..., Planning Work Program, 1986-1987 (Box 2)
  - ... Transit System, Annual Report, 1985 (Box 2)
  - ... Airport, Annual Report, 1971; 5 Land Use Plan Maps (Box 2)
  - ... Solid Waste Disposal District, Evaluation ... Refuse-to-Energy System, 1979 (Box 2)
  - Steele Memorial Library ..., Annual Report, 1972 (Box 2)
  - Council of Community Services ... Sixteenth Annual Report, 1970-1971 (Box 2)
  - HUD, Region II, New Elmira Urban Renewal Project, Final Environmental Impact Statement, 1976 (Box 2)
  - Market Analysis of the Elmira-Corning Housing Market Area, 1973 (Box 2)
  - The General Plan of Big Flats, n.d. (Box 2)
  - Chemung River Basin, Regional Water Resources Planning Board, Tentative Board Plan, ca. 1974 (Box 2)
  - Chemung River Basin, Regional Water Resources Planning Board, Tentative Plan Summary, 1975 (Box 2)
  - Chemung River Basin, Flood Warning Support Corp., Annual Report, 1982 (Box 2)
- Series XII. Steuben County planning documents
  - ... Planning Board, Annual Report, 1971-1973, 1975-1977, 1979-1980 (Box 2)
  - ... Bicentennial Committee, Newsletter, #2-6, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
  - ... Traffic Safety Board, Second Annual Report, 1969 (Box 2)
  - Highway Department, Kanakadea Recreational Area Committee and the Parks Committee, Annual Report, 1969 (Box 2)
  - Highway Department, Kanakadea Recreational Area, Management Program, 1971 (Box 2)
  - Intergovernmental Council of Southeast ..., Annual Report, 1977-1982 (Box 2)
  - Southeast ... Area Planning Board, Annual Report, 1970-1980 (Box 2)
  - Southeast ... Area Planning Board, Minutes, 1971-1973 (Box 2)
  - Project Agnes, 1974 (Box 2)
  - Project '76: Recreating a Community (Box 2)
  - Career Development Council, Inc.: The First Five Years, 1980 (Box 2)
- Series XIII. Miscellaneous planning documents
  - Forest Resources and Wood Using Industries of Six Southwestern New York Counties, 1979 (Box 3)
  - Forest Resource Management and Industrial Development Study, Steuben and Allegany Counties, 5 vols., 1980-1981 (Box 3)
  - Peek, J.R., Electrical Generation from Wood, 1976 (Box 3)
  - Hazen Agricultural Products, Cohocton, NY, Proposal for Ethanol Production Facility, 2 vols., 1980 (Box 3)
  - Agrionics Corp., Walworth, NY, Feasibility Study for Fuel Grade Ethanol Plant, 2 vols., 1980 (Box 3)
  - Braithwaite, Douglas C. and Harold R. Capener, The Feasibility of Methane Production from Dairy Animal Wastes: The Farmer's Perspective, CU (Box 3)
  - NYS, Office of Planning Coordination, Development Plan, Proposed 1990 Land Use, Map (Box 3)
  - Cortland County Planning Department, Land Use Plan, Map, 1977 (Box 3)
  - Owego Environmental Study, CU, 1974 (Box 3)
  - Economic Impact of Paper Products Manufacturing on the Clinton County Economy, CU, 1977 (Box 3)
  - Oneida County Department of Planning, Herkimer-Oneida Counties Comprehensive Planning Program, Annual Report, 1974 (Box 3)
  - Energy Conserving Site Design, Case Study--Radisson, NY, DOE, 1979 (Box 3)
  - Monroe County, Town of Greece, Parks and Recreation Master Plan, 1973 (Box 3)
  - Monroe County, Town of Greece, Comprehensive Planning and Management Assistance Program, Application for Participation, 1976 (Box 3)
  - Monroe County, Town of Greece, Dorsey Road Impacts, 1976 (Box 3)
  - Scottsville, NY, Proposed Subdivision Regulations, 1970 (Box 3)
  - Mechanicville, NY, Economic Development Plan ..., 1978 (Box 3)
  - Mount Vernon, NY, Economic Development Study, 1972 (Box 3)
  - Black River-St. Lawrence Regional Planning Board, Housing Needs Analysis, Technical Series Report No. 17, 1976 (Box 3)
  - Proceedings, Third Environmental Leaders' Forum, "Shared Resources--Yours, Mine, or Ours?", CU, 1974 (Box 3)
  - Proceedings, Symposium on Energy for Local Government, "Extending Energy Resources," CU, 1978 (Box 3)
  - [Proceedings,] Nuclear Waste Symposium, Sponsored by Congressman Stanley N. Lundine, 39th Congressional District, 1979 (Box 3)
  - USDA, Forest Service, Eastern Region, Land and Resource Management Plan, Final Environmental Impact Statement, and Record of Decision, Green Mountain National Forest and Finger Lakes National Forest, 4 vols., 1986 (Box 3)
  - Union Carbide Corp., Nuclear Division, Plans for Environmental Surveys of Bedded Salt Formations ... of the Salina Basin in NY, 2 vols., 1978 (Box 3)
  - City Planning Commission, Plan for New York City, 2 vols., 1969 (Box 3)